<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Stuffed</title>
    <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Get Stuffed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:55:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MedamesBeans</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/medamesbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/medamesbeans/</guid>
      <description>Perfect ful medames Prep 10 min, plus soaking time if using dried Cook 20 min-70 min, depending on the type of bean Serves 4-6
400g small dried fava beans, or 2 x 400g tins 1 tsp cumin seeds 2-4 garlic cloves, peeled Salt 2 tbsp extra-virgin olive oil, plus extra to serve 1 large onion, peeled and finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 1 green chilli, finely chopped (optional) 1 lemon 1 small bunch flat-leaf parsley</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FrenchToast</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/frenchtoast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 19:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/frenchtoast/</guid>
      <description>Nigellas Parmesan French Toast
INGREDIENTS Serves: 1-2
1 large egg 3 x 15ml tablespoons finely grated Parmesan ¼ teaspoon paprika 1 teaspoon Dijon mustard ½ teaspoon Worcestershire sauce 3 x 15ml tablespoons full fat milk 2 slices white sourdough bread or anything sturdy and with a bit of bite to it 1 x 15ml tablespoon unsalted butter ½ teaspoon regular olive oil
TO SERVE:
flatleaf parsley spring onions
METHOD
 Whisk the egg, Parmesan, paprika, mustard, Worcestershire sauce and milk together in a shallow dish that the slices of bread will fit in with not a great deal of space around them, making sure everything is completely combined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brussels Sprouts Kimchi</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/kimchi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/kimchi/</guid>
      <description>How-to-turn-excess-sprouts-into-kimchi-recipe-zero-waste-cooking
Makes 2 x 500g jars
500g brussels sprouts, and/or other greens 250g mixed seasonal vegetables (eg, carrots, jerusalem artichokes, squash, turnip, kohlrabi) 100g dark green leek tops or spring onions Sea salt 4 tbsp brown rice, or white rice flour, gluten-free flour or wheat flour 6 garlic cloves, peeled 1 small red or white onion, peeled 4 tbsp gochujang, or Korean chilli powder or red chilli flakes 50ml fish sauce</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken and Chorizo Paella</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/paella/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/paella/</guid>
      <description>Easy One Pot Chicken and Chorizo Paella
Easy One Pot Chicken and Chorizo Paella This easy one pot Chicken and Chorizo Paella is perfect for busy evenings when you have very little time to cook but still want a great tasting meal!
Course Main Course, One Pot Cuisine Spanish Prep Time 10 minutes Cook Time 30 minutes Total Time 40 minutes Servings 4 people Calories 734kcal Author Eb Gargano
Ingredients</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SalmonMac</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/salmonmac/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 18:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/salmonmac/</guid>
      <description>Nigel Slater&amp;rsquo;s salmon macaroni recipe
The recipe Pour 600ml of double cream into a saucepan, add 400g of salmon, a little black pepper and a bay leaf and bring almost to the boil. Lower the heat and let the salmon cook gently for about 10 minutes until the flesh comes apart with ease, then remove from the heat.
Boil 150g of serpentelli or macaroni in generously salted water for nine minutes then drain and tip into a baking dish.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
