<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Beans on Get Stuffed</title>
    <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/tags/beans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Beans on Get Stuffed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:41:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/tags/beans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EggsAndBeans</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/eggsandbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 15:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/eggsandbeans/</guid>
      <description>Scrambled eggs with beans
These Scrambled Eggs with Beans, known as Revuelto con Alubias Blancas, are possibly one of the most underrated dishes ever. We’re talking a ton of great flavors, seriously easy to make and all done in just 20 minutes. Serve them for breakfast or even for dinner, and always next to some Catalan Tomato Bread.
To make this recipe, I used canned white beans. Just to make this quicker and easier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Butter Cannellini Beans Cavolo Greens</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/buttercannellinibeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/buttercannellinibeans/</guid>
      <description>Butter Beans Cannellini and Cavolo Nero
Beans in jars are more plump and juicy than those in tins, but either works well here. It is essential to include some of the aquafaba – the bottling liquor. It adds a creamy quality without the need for any dairy produce. Serves 2
cavolo nero 150g hispi (pointed) cabbage 200g garlic 2 plump cloves olive oil 2 tbsp dill 2 tbsp butter beans 400g cannellini beans 250g lemon 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medames Beans</title>
      <link>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/medamesbeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 10:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://redbands.github.io/getStuffed/posts/medamesbeans/</guid>
      <description>Perfect ful medames Prep 10 min, plus soaking time if using dried Cook 20 min-70 min, depending on the type of bean Serves 4-6
400g small dried fava beans, or 2 x 400g tins 1 tsp cumin seeds 2-4 garlic cloves, peeled Salt 2 tbsp extra-virgin olive oil, plus extra to serve 1 large onion, peeled and finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 1 green chilli, finely chopped (optional) 1 lemon 1 small bunch flat-leaf parsley</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
